Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
（岸本(きしもと)）アア…
（聖(せい)）なんで
急に こんななってんだろう？
How did this happen all of a sudden...
and in a place like this?
こんな所で…
I thought I was dead.
死んだと思ってたのにな
We're not dead.
（計(けい)）死んでないよ
でも 死んでるのに気持ちよかった
But it sure felt good even if I'm dead...
Oh boy...
あらら…
（計）いいよ 別に
Ah, who cares.
I'll Do It!
Please go eliminate these targets now, you bastards.
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
（コンタ）
あばれんぼう星人？
Please go eliminate these targets now, you bastards.
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
"Ferocious alien"?
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
（トマオ）
意味 分かんねえ
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
I don't get it.
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
I don't get it.
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
What does it mean?
（宮藤(みやふじ)）
何が言いたいんだ？
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
I think you mean "Ferocious SHOGUN"!
（池(いけ)）
将軍じゃねえのかよ
（宮藤）
全部 君の言ったとおりになる
Every time you say something's
going to happen, it does.
What are you anyway?
何なんだ？ 君は
It's not just me.
（加藤(かとう)）俺だけじゃない
こっち側にいる人間は―
All of us on this side of the room were here...
前から ここにいたっつうか
来たことがあるんだ
Or rather, we've been here before.
ここの法則に関して
そっちより少し知ってる程度だけど
Although we only know a little more
about the rules than you guys do.
It should open soon, so be careful.
そろそろ開くから気をつけてくれ
もうすぐだ
Any second now.
（宮藤たち）ウワッ！
早く着替えてきたほうがいい
（岸本）うん
You should go change quick.
Okay.
（岡崎(おかざき)）ウホホ～！
Wow, look at the details...
（宮藤）へえ… よくできてるな
There are suits in this container,
so grab one and put it on!
こっちのケースに
スーツが入ってるから着てくれ
１人ずつ ちゃんとあるから
There's one for each of you.
Don't let him fool you, you morons!
（徳川(とくがわ)）
惑わされるな　このバカ者どもが！
ここは試しの場所と言っただろう！
Didn't I tell you this is the place of trial?
Listen, that is not a human.
That is the symbol of foul passion!
よいか？ あれは人ではない
あれは煩悩の象徴だ
Those who choose to follow him will
be defeated by greed and go to Hell!
ヤツについていく者こそ
欲に負け 地獄に落ちる者
What you have in your hand right now
is a tool to kill others!
お前たちが手にしている物は
人殺す物だ！
Hey, wait a minute!
ちょっと待ってくれ！
I'm a human just like the rest of you.
俺は あんたらと同じ人間だ
信じてくれ！
Believe me!
Don't let him get to you!
He only APPEARS to be human!
（徳川）惑わされるな！
そう見えているだけだ！
Whatever, man. I don't get it...
（コンタ）ワケ分かんねえ
You'll die if you listen to this priest!
この坊さんの言うこと聞くと
死んじまうことになるぞ
ハハハハッ…
死んだ人間が集まってるんだぞ
Everyone gathered here IS dead!
（加藤）あれ？ どうしたんだ？
What's wrong?
Uh, Kurono's already back there, so...
（岸本）あの… 玄野(くろの)君がいたから
Kei? What's he doing?
（加藤）計ちゃん？ 何してんだ？
The suits...
スーツ…
（聖）はぁ？ なに？
What?
You should put one on...
スーツ着たほうが…
（聖）そ… そう？
O... Okay...
What is this thing?
I don't understand what it's for.
（聖）何なの？ これ
全然 意味 分かんないんだけど
（計）そのうち分かるよ
You'll find out soon enough.
（聖）なんで？
この服 私にあつらえた物みたい
Why does it fit as if
it was made just for me?
Heaven is completely different
from what I expected.
天国って
想像したとこと 全然 違う
I already told you we're not dead.
だから 死んでないって
（加藤）計ちゃん… うん？
Kei?
Excuse me...
（岸本）あの…
（聖）えっ？
Oh, nothing...
いえ…
（加藤）ここにいてやるよ
（岸本）えっ？
I'll stay with you.
You were in danger the last time
and the time before that, remember?
この間も
その前もヤバかっただろう？
I don't want anything
to happen to you again so...
また何かあるといけないから…
（岸本）あ… ありがとう
Thanks...
（徳川）
南無阿弥陀仏　南無阿弥陀仏
Namu Amida Butsu...
Namu Amida Butsu... Namu Amida Butsu...
南無阿弥陀仏　南無阿弥陀仏
Namu Amida Butsu...
Namu Amida Butsu... Namu Amida Butsu...
この連中に どうにかして
スーツ着てもらわねえと
I need to get these guys
to put on the suits somehow.
Namu Amida Butsu... Namu Amida Butsu...
Why even bother?
いいんじゃねえの？ 別に
Namu Amida Butsu...
俺らだけで
なんとかなるんじゃねえか？
Don't you think we should
be able to handle it on our own?
Namu Amida Butsu...
Don't you think we should
be able to handle it on our own?
Namu Amida Butsu... Namu Amida Butsu...
（岸本）玄野君 そんな…
（加藤）ああ 誰も死なせたくない
Kurono! You've got to be kidding!
I don't want anyone to die.
（加藤）１人でも多く
協力してもらったほうが―
The more of us there are,
the greater the chance we all survive.
全員が生き残れる確率が上がるんだ
Looks like you're
interested in guns, too huh?
おたくも銃好きそうだな
シット…
Shit.
聞いていいかな？ いろいろと
（加藤）あ… ああ
Could I ask you a few questions?
Uh... sure.
The man inside of the ball...
あの玉の中の男　あれ なに？
What is that?
I'm not sure...
（加藤）さあ？
（宮藤）分かんないの？
You don't know?
Okay, then tell me who's
the sponsor of this club.
じゃあさ 誰なの？ この会の主催者
"Sponsor"? I don't know.
（加藤）主催者？ さあ？
You don't know?
Huh, you don't know anything then.
“さあ”って…
なんだ 何も知らないのか
すいません
I'm sorry.
So then just like it said on the ball,
…で あの玉に出てきたように―
これから その服を着て武器持って
何とか星人 殺しに行くわけ？
we're going to put on those suits and
go kill some aliens with these weapons?
Yes, that's right.
はい そうッス
And these aliens, or whatever...
何とか星人って あれ なに？
宇宙人？
what about them?
Are they from outer space?
（トマオ）フッ…
（コンタ）…んだ？ それ
What the hell! Aliens?
宇宙人ってかよ
Probably...
多分…
You saw the ball draw out living people
with its laser earlier, right?
（宮藤）
さっき そこの玉が レーザーで
人間を描き出すところを見た
Can today's human technology
even do stuff like that?
あんなこと
今の人間の技術でできるか？
それとも 神か仏の仕業か
Or is it some act of God or Buddha?
Who cares if it's a divine act or not?
（池）いいでしょう　神でも何でも
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
As far as I can see,
（宮藤）
僕が思うに この玉は なにか―
Grumpy Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Ferocious Alien
Catch Phrase:
Hmph!
I think this is some type of teleportation device,
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
I think this is some type of teleportation device,
ＳＦに出てくる
転送器みたいな物のような気がする
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
Just like you see in sci-fi movies.
Please go eliminate these targets now, you bastards.
Ferocious Alien
Traits:
Powerful
Big
Likes:
Tight places,
the Grumpy Alien
Catch Phrase:
Ha!
Just like you see in sci-fi movies.
I don't know exactly how it works
仕組みは分かんないけど
人が死ぬ瞬間
別の空間に移動させる機械とか…
but it's possible that it can teleport a person
to a different place the second he dies.
ハハハッ… ばかばかしい
That's ridiculous!
You said we'd die if we don't
wear this suit, didn't you?
このスーツを着ないと
死ぬとか言ってたね？
It's more like it would lower
your chance of surviving.
死ぬっつうか
生き延びる確率が減る
…んじゃ 着るよ
Okay then, I'll put it on.
（北条(ほうじょう)）あっ…
（加藤）始まったぞ
It's starting!
Please Go
Kato, look.
加藤君 あれ
（加藤）あ… ああ
Oh...
It used to be 60 minutes...
So that means...
今まで60分だったよな？
てことは…
We might have to deal with
something even worse than before...
そんだけ すっげえ相手ってことか
It's no big deal.
関係ねえよ 30分ぐらい…
やってやるぜ
It's only an extra 30 minutes.
I'm up for it.
Look at them. They're going to Hell.
見ろ！ 地獄に落ちるぞ あいつらは
早く！
全員 この服を着てくれ　死ぬぞ！
Hurry up! All of you!
Put the suit on NOW or you'll die!
Who would wear that gay shit?
着るかよ んな物(もん)　だせえ…
That's like something
an otaku would wear. Gross!
オタクっぽくて気持ち悪い
C'mon, what happened to the reciting?
お前ら 念仏が止まっているぞ！
…つうか 念仏 もういいや
（トマオ）俺ん家(ち) 仏教じゃねえし
I'm done with that.
I'm not Buddhist anyway.
We have no choice!
もう しょうがないよ
私たちだけで なんとかするしか…
We have to take care of this on our own!
Stop it! Hey, let me down!
（トマオ）やめろ 下ろせ！
（コンタ）何すんだ！
Cut it out! What the hell are you doing?
Stop it! Hey, let me down!
いてっ！
（コンタ）鉄か！
Ow!
What's he made of? Steel?
That's the power this suit possesses.
これが この服の力だ
This suit can protect you.
（加藤）
この服は お前らを守ってくれる
You don't need to wear it right now.
（加藤）今すぐ着なくてもいい
手に持っててくれ
Just take it with you.
Ratenin
Where are we?
どこだ？ ここ
A temple?
寺？
一緒に転送されんなよ てめえ！
How dare you get transported with me!
（室戸(むろと)）
今日さ 何の歌にしよっか？
Hey, which song you wanna sing today?
I'll let you decide it.
（梶浦(かじうら)）お前(めえ) 決めろや
（室戸）う～ん…
Hmm...
ラジオ体操の歌 覚えてる？
You remember that radio calisthenics song?
（梶浦）
ああ？ あ～ 分かる 分かる
Huh? Oh yeah, I do, I do.
Let's go with that.
（室戸）
じゃ あれね　ノリいいかもよ
Could be a good beat to work with.
That creeps me out no matter
how many times I see it.
（コンタ）
何回見ても気持ち悪いな これ
Take a look. They're falling into
the pits of Hell one by one.
（徳川）
見ろ！ 次々に地獄に落ちていくぞ
Divine judgment has now begun.
裁きが始まったのだ！
What kind of place is Hell anyway?
あのさ
地獄って どんなとこ？ これ夢？
Is this a dream?
Please Go
Am I going to Hell?
俺 地獄に行っちゃうわけ？
あっ… アア… た… 助けて！
Please Go
Help me!
Don't worry.
大丈夫　地獄になんか行かない
外に出るだけだ
You're not going to Hell.
You're just going outside.
南無阿弥…
Namu Amishinrai... Butsu...
Look, you don't need to put them on right now...
（加藤）
とにかく 今着なくていいから―
But I want you to hold on
to the suits and the weapons!
Namu Amishinrai... Butsu...
スーツと銃は手に持っててくれ！
And wherever we end up,
don't try to leave or go anywhere else.
それから 次の場所へ行っても
帰ったりしないでくれ
あっ…
（岸本）加藤君
Kato...
I'll see you outside. Don't worry.
外で会おう　大丈夫
（岸本）うん
Okay...
大丈夫だ
We'll be okay.
喝！ 拙僧(せっそう)の話に耳を傾けぬから
こういうことになるのだ！
This is what happens when
you ignore the words of a priest!
All of you might as well go to Hell!
全員 地獄に落ちるがよい！
Someone!
誰か！ 神さま！ アアッ！
Please, God!
Please Go
Listen, everyone! Do NOT leave this place!
（加藤）
みんな ここから離れないでくれ
You think maybe we shouldn't have done it?
（聖）やっぱ マズかったかな？
It doesn't matter.
（計）別に
（聖）…なら いいけど
Well, if you say so...
Hey, what's the big deal about this place?
（コンタ）
あのな 何てことねえじゃねえかよ
I bet we could just go home from here.
（トマオ）
これ 帰れんじゃねえの？
（加藤）
待ってくれ　離れないほうがいい
Wait! You should stay here with us!
（コンタ）
フン… いつまで寝言こいてんだよ
How long are you gonna be talkin'
nonsense like that?
なんだ 羅鼎院(らていいん)じゃねえか
What? Isn't this Ratenin?
Hey, mister priest,
you were crying, weren't you?
坊さん 泣いてたろう？
（徳川）何を言う！
What are you talking about?
It might be a better idea to accept this.
（宮藤）これ 受け入れたほうが
よかないですかね？
どうも その… まともな状況じゃ…
This doesn't seem remotely ordinary...
What the hell?
（池）
な～んだ… 近くの駅から帰るか
Well, I guess I'll catch a train
from the nearest station.
They're still running, right?
まだ電車あるよな？
You can't leave! Please stay here!
（岸本）帰っちゃダメ　ここにいて
（池）はい？ なんで？
Huh? Why?
（岸本）だから
さっき加藤君が言ったとおり…
Because it's just like Kato said earlier...
Yeah, yeah, aliens, right?
はいはい 宇宙人ね
If I end up running late for work tomorrow,
I'll be sure to tell my supervisor about them.
あした遅刻したら
課長に そう言い訳しときますよ
ダメ！
（加藤）マズイな
Don't go!
This isn't good...
（計）息ぴったりじゃねえかよ
ふざけんなよ！
Look at these two... Give me a break!
（池）タクシー！ ンッ…
Hey, taxi!
Those are the same Buddha statues
that were displayed on the ball, aren't they?
（北条）この仏像だよな？
あの玉のモニターに出てたの
So are they supposed to be
the aliens or whatever?
（聖）これなの？ 何とか星人って
I don't know.
（加藤）分からない
We always run into weak ones and strong ones...
So, I can't tell which these might be...
いつも 弱いのと強いのがいるから
これが どっちかまでは…
どこかな？ あっ においすんなぁ
Where are they?
Mmm, I can smell it.
あっち あっち
This way, this way.
インスタントラーメンですか
Instant ramen, huh?
Man, they ignored me again!
（池）
また乗車拒否かよ！ 駅まで歩くか
I guess I'll walk to the station.
（加藤）待ってくれ！
（コンタ）うるせえよ
Wait!
Shut up!
（トマオ）帰るぜ オタク野郎
We're outta here, you fuckin' otaku!
（徳川）まったく… 誰だ？ こんな
手の込んだ いたずらをしたのは
Who in the world would play such an
elaborate joke like this on us?
Wait!
（加藤）ま… 待ってくれ！
帰らないでくれ！ おい！
Please don't leave! Hey!
加藤 放っとけって！
Kato! Just leave them alone!
（加藤）えっ？
（計）あんなヤツら―
I said just leave those assholes alone!
放っとけって言ってんだよ
Kurono, we just can't do that...
（岸本）玄野君 そういうわけには
They won't believe anything we say.
（計）何を言ってもムダだ
それより 早く戦おうぜ
More importantly... let's go kick some ass...
since we got more time today.
今日 時間いっぱいあるみたいだし
（加藤）計ちゃん…
Kei...
What are you talking about, Kurono?
玄野君 何を言ってるの？
（加藤）
と… とにかく そこで待っててくれ
Look, you guys just wait here, okay?
（トマオ）頭が…
（加藤）どいて！
Move!
ウッ… 酒くせえ
Ugh, he reeks of alcohol...
This is what'll happen if you go any further!
これ以上 進んでみろ！
こいつと同じに 頭が吹き飛ぶぞ！
Your head will be blown up just like his!
What the hell?
（コンタ）な… 何だよ
（徳川）これが裁きというものか…
I suppose this is divine judgment...
He absolutely reeks of alcohol!
This smell has to be brandy or maybe whisky...
それにしても酒くさい
この においは
ブランデーか ウイスキーか？
No, it's not divine judgment
or anything like that!
違う　裁きなんかじゃない！
とにかく 門の所まで戻ってくれ！
C'mon, just go back to the gate!
What was THAT?
今の なに？
Beats me...
さあ？
“裁き”とかってやつじゃねえの？
Isn't that divine judgment
or something?
よく分かんねえけど
Not that I'd know...
I guess no one's head would go flying off
like that if this were a survival game...
サバイバルゲームとかじゃ
人の頭 飛ばねえもんな
Heh, these are nice.
フフッ… いいじゃんよ これ
Hey, what are you talking about?
（岸本）
ちょ… ちょっと 何言ってるの？
（岡崎）別に
Nothing...
That looks good.
（室戸）おいしそうだね
（男性）うん？
Shall we show you the best way to eat it?
それさぁ いちばんおいしい食べ方
教えてあげよっか？
That's hot!
アッ… あちっ… ウワッ…
It's the beginning of a brand new day!
A day filled with hope!
Hey, come back here! You homeless shit!
こら 逃げんじゃねえよ
（男性）アア… 助けてくれ
（梶浦）
ホームレスのくせに　ハハハハッ…
（北条）
どうする？ 力ずくで開けるか？
What are we gonna do?
Should we open it by force?
確かに こん中だな
入っていいのか？
It looks like they're in there for sure.
Can we really go in?
We don't have any other choice, do we?
それっきゃねえだろう
Everyone, stay back.
みんな 後ろに下がって
（岸本）どうするの？
What are you gonna do?
For now, I'm gonna try to break this gate.
とりあえず 門 ぶち破ってみる
計ちゃん？
（計）俺がやるよ
Kei?
I'll do it.
（計）中に入って とにかく
敵を倒せばいいんだろう？
We just have to go in there
and kill the enemies, right?
早く行こうぜ
Let's hurry up!
You fool!
（徳川）こら 貴様！
（計）うん？
（徳川）
仮にも寺の門だぞ　何をするのだ！
That is a temple gate!
What do you think you're doing?!
Shut up!
（計）うるせえな！
こうでもしねえと
あいつらには勝てねえんだよ
I have to do this or we'll never beat them!
This is what you call a preemptive strike!
先制攻撃ってやつだよ
You'll be damned for sure!
まったく バチ当たりが！
一体 寺を何と心得て…
What do you take this place for?!
This is a temple!
Everyone, listen up!
（加藤）みんな よく聞いてくれ！
We're about to risk our lives
fighting some unknown creatures!
今から 俺らは
全員の生存を懸けて―
正体不明の生き物と戦争する！
This is not a game! This is real!
ゲームとかじゃなく マジにだ！
このスーツは
体を超人のようにしてくれる
These suits will give you super powers.
Remember you must pull both triggers
at the same time to fire the guns!
銃の引き金は
２ついっぺんに引かないと撃てない
制限時間内に
全部 倒さなきゃならないんだ
And we have to defeat all our enemies
within the time limit!
Many people have died so far!
今までに何人も死んだ
これは本物の戦争なんだ！
This is a real war!
War... So this is for real...
戦争… やっぱり
I'm gonna fuckin' kill them...
ぶっ殺してやるぜ
あのさ やっぱり気になるんだけど
This is kind of bothering me, but...
Are you sure those things aren't the aliens?
何とか星人って
やっぱ あれなんじゃない？
Can they even move?
（北条）これが動くのか？
（加藤）よく分かんないけど―
I don't know, but they seem too big,
at least compared to other ones we've fought.
今までのヤツらに比べて
でかすぎると思うんだ
I've never seen any enemies like these.
こんなの会ったことない
Maybe they're not it, then...
（宮藤）違うのかな？
According to the radar,
they're inside this temple, right?
（北条）
レーダーだと 寺ん中なんだろう？
Yeah...
（加藤）ああ…
（宮藤）何か確かめる方法ないの？
Isn't there any way to find out for sure?
How about using the X-gun?
（岸本）Ｘガンは？
（北条）Ｘガン？
X-gun?
Umm...
（加藤）あっ… いや…
（宮藤）Ｘガン？
X-gun?
撃ったときＸの形になるし
We call it the X-gun because
it creates an X-shape when you fire.
The X also stands for "x-ray."
あと レントゲンの
“Ｘレイ”の“Ｘ”で Ｘガン
Kato came up with the name.
加藤君が付けたのよね
そんなの いつの間に付けてんだよ
When the hell'd he name that?
And how does Kishimoto know about it?!
しかも
岸本 なんで そんなの知ってんだ？
It's not an official name or anything...
だから 正式名称じゃないんだけど
ふ～ん…
いいんじゃないか Ｘガン
Hmm, X-gun, huh? It sounds good.
So, what can this X-gun do?
それで
そのＸガンで何ができるの？
You should be able to see through
an object with it, right?
（岸本）Ｘガンで見れば―
レントゲンみたいに
透けるでしょう？
That's right...
（加藤）そうか
生物なら骨とか映るかもしれない
If they're living creatures, we should
be able to see their bones and stuff!
マジかよ…
No way...
What's wrong?
（北条）どうした？
（加藤）どうすんだ？ こんな…
How are we supposed to fight them...
生きてる… 生物だ　間違いない
They're alive. They're living creatures...
I'm positive...
Kishimoto...
岸本 あいつ撃てねえよ
He can't shoot it.
でも
そんなこと言ってる場合じゃ…
But... We don't have time for that!
（コンタ）
何だ？ 宇宙人ってマジ？
Hey, so these things really are aliens?
Are they gonna move?
（トマオ）これ動くのかよ？
What now?
どうする？
（加藤）あっ…
Can't we just get them right now
since they're not moving?
動いてねえから
やれんじゃねえの？ 今
捕獲用の銃で俺が撃ってみる
I'll try it with the trap gun!
Kato...
（岸本）加藤君…
（加藤）誰か持っていないか？
Does anyone have one?
（宮藤）返せよ？
You better give it back.
Wait, Kato.
（計）待てよ 加藤
（加藤）えっ？
Open your heart to happiness...
And look up at the big, blue sky...
（加藤）計ちゃん？
Kei...
（計）まだるっこしいんだよ！
（加藤）えっ？
This is frustrating!
捕獲もクソもあるか！
１発で しとめりゃいいんだよ
Screw trying to capture it!
All you need to do is kill it with a single shot!
（加藤）だけど 計ちゃん…
（岸本）玄野君
But still...
Kurono...
（計）俺がやる
I'll do it!
This is the fastest way to do it!
このほうが手っとり早いんだよ！
（引き金を握る音）
（徳川）ウワーッ！
What was that?
何だ？ ありゃ
I bet it's a traffic accident or
something. Not our problem.
どうせ 交通事故か何かだろう
関係ねえよ
Listen to the voice on the radio...
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
These guys aren't bad at all.
（北条）
案外イケてんじゃん こいつら
まとまってきてるよな
They've actually started working together.
Huh? No, I'm NOT! Don't look at me like that!
ああ？ 違うって！
俺のこと そういう目で見るな！
I told you I'm NORMAL!
だから 俺はノーマルだって！
Next episode: I Can Shoot Them, Can't I?
次回
“こいつら撃っていいんだろ？”